A Journey in Search of Tea Baking in Shiga Prefecture
Eh, wait, I want to eat Aria's white roast.
Ah, kitchen
A Journey in Search of Tea Bowl in Shiga Prefecture
So... we're in Shiga Prefecture, near Hikone Castle.
Have you ever been to Shiga Prefecture other than for a live performance?
No, I haven't.
No?
I'm glad to hear that.
My brother is a train driver.
So many Shinkansen trains pass through a place called Maebaru Station.
I often come to Maebaru Station to catch the Shinkansen.
There was a bento box lunch of red konnyaku
I have such fond memories of eating it.
To be honest, I haven't been able to see the sights like this.
Then today is perfect.
It's perfect for tea.
Specialties?
I'm looking forward to eating and seeing the sights.
Look at this!
Look at that!
Beginning? Beginning? Beginning?
Shoo! Shh!
I'd like to go to Castle Road now.
Oh, my God, that looks so good. Delicious steak.
This place is amazing.
It's like Kyoto, you know? It's like Kyoto.
Wow, it's so nice!
It's so Japan. It's so Japan.
I think people who like historical dramas will love it.
What's this? It's dinner time. Sukiyaki.
Sukiyaki? Looks delicious!
Oh, it's just a little low-priced.
Wow.
Shall I take it? Thank you.
Mont Blanc.
Looks delicious.
They have iced monaca.
Oh, I love the patisseries.
Wait, this place is nice.
This place is really nice.
It's like a real castle. It's like a castle street.
I thought this place was interesting, too.
I thought this might be the entrance to Hikone Castle.
But you're right...
No, it wasn't.
It's got that much atmosphere.
What's with all that smoke? Look, right in front of you.
Tsukudani?
A burger?
A tsukudani burger. - A tsukudani burger?
They're cooking... Meat and stuff.
I see.
There's a big crowd.
What's with that street?
I heard it's a romantic town.
But you're right.
This red lamp has a Showa-era feel.
I wonder if there's something there.
It's so nice.
I want to wear a kimono.
Wait, that's nice.
I want to go sightseeing in a kimono.
Wear a kimono.
A Mayuko experience would be nice.
There's a helmet.
This looks like a Gonyang.
I can wear it.
See?
Good night.
Look, in the middle.
Oh, my God.
It's a wakashiya.
Retro town.
Oh, cucumbers!
You love cucumbers, don't you?
Cucumbers are my favorite food at festivals.
Cucumbers at a festival stall... you can choose ume (plum) or
You can choose soy bean sauce or miso paste.
I like miso.
I like miso the best.
I like lemon.
Lemon is good.
Oh, my God.
There's so many different kinds.
I need something salty.
You know what I mean? You know what I mean?
Let me know if you want some. Don't hesitate.
Thank you.
But we have everything here.
If you want something sweet, I'm sure you'll love the mmm blanc.
If you want something salty, there are skewers.
Like those skewers.
That's right, that's right.
Like the ones you can find at a food stall.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
So you can feel Shiga Prefecture.
It's perfect.
What? Look, goldfish!
Oh, no, no, no!
What a beautiful simulation!
Thank you very much.
Walk here, everyone. Walk and discover the goldfish.
There are goldfish.
It's beautiful, isn't it? It would be more festive.
I'm curious at night.
It's so beautiful at night.
You'll see when you get here.
I don't think it's oyakodon. It's not pudding. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
Look, it's not cute. She keeps crossing her arms.
She's so reassuring, really.
Really.
Crossing your arms makes you feel even more secure.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're so cute!
Thank you.
I'm on a bit of a salt kick right now.
I'm munching on some normal food.
I'm sorry.
It's a little hot in here.
I had heat stroke.
Oh, my God.
Can we turn people away now?
Skewer!
Wait, I want some grilled ayu.
I want some.
I want it!
I want this.
I want some!
I like tasty chimmi.
I'll have some Ainu miss leeks.
Please do.
I'm looking forward to it.
It smells so good!
I love it!
Ayu. I love grilled ayu.
It's like it's from Diaco.
Really... volunteer.
I can feel your determination.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
It's so big!
Now that's what I'm talking about.
That's right.
And we like new flavors.
We have a little taste for cafeterias, don't we?
That's why this one.
Bon appétit!
I chose this one.
I don't know how to eat it.
How am I going to eat it?
Can I just bite into it?
Can I bite into the steak?
Oh, it's hot!
Dokka!
Dokka-dokka!
It's too good!
It's absolutely delicious!
It's so soft and chewy.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I'm a bit of a picky eater.
I'm very picky.
It's delicious.
It's really good.
Crispy.
Really good.
Not quite picture-perfect
Really delicious
Sorry, but I'll eat it
Delicious
It's delicious.
Doesn't it feel fresh?
I can feel it so much.
I can feel the whitening.
I ate it.
Miso is delicious!
I ate it all!
Thank you for the food!
It was so delicious!
I have experienced catching, skewering and grilling ayu fish by myself, but it was so different from the taste of ayu fish.
But it tasted so different from that.
The violets were also very tasty.
I know what you mean. It was delicious.
Thank you for the food.
Yes, I'm going for a walk around Shikoku Castle.
Wow!
Have you ever been to Shikoku Castle?
No, I haven't. I know Shikoku Castle, though. Me neither.
I haven't been to Shikoku Castle yet.
I don't know what the outer walls are.
Stonewalls, huh? It has a certain atmosphere. The stone walls are magnificent.
I'm going to the sun.
The city is surrounded by dazzling light.
It's Lonely. Lonely.
I'll be buried in such a crowd.
Invisible stars in the sky.
Let's speak English!
Okay, I'm going to play the "No Japanese allowed" game.
Let's start!
So...
What do you want to go to Japan?
One more time
Where do you want to go to in Japan?
Now?
The future?
In the future
I want to go to Japan
Yes, I do.
I want to go to Japan.
I want to go there
I want to go there.
Miyako Island
Yes, I like it.
I like it! Me too!
I want to go to Okinawa!
Yes!
I'm a genius!
Blue Seal Ice Cream
Benimo
Tart
Chocolate mint.
Really?
Hello, everybody!
Hello everyone!
This is Natsume Nakayama!
Violet Toshiro.
Nice to meet you.
No, no, no, I'm Katherine.
Katherine? Really?
Catherine.
Elizabeth.
Elizabeth, yes.
Katherine.
Katherine, hello.
I'm really serious. We speak English in real life.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, but you know what?
It's working.
I know who's successful.
Yeah.
I also know that I won't slip.
You want to go to Miyakojima Island, right?
That's right.
Auctions Beauty Salon.
Yes, Auchon Beauty Salon.
Like this.
Nope.
Please try it, everyone!
The "No Japanese Allowed" game.
It's a real crowd pleaser.
I'll be really excited.
Awesome mailbox!
There's Hikone Castle on top of the mailbox!
Wait, it's real.
Did you see it?
Wait, that's amazing.
Amazing!
Wonderful!
Rickshaw.
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh!
Wow
Ah, Yunaka
I did it!
I want to play with Hikonyan's gacha gacha.
Can I show you something? This store.
I want to see.
May I?
I want to buy some Hikonyan stuff for Madopi.
Lots of stuff.
Really? Can we use them?
Can you put in a batch?
I'll put in a batch.
Do you want to put in a compilation?
It's good, isn't it?
This one, the gold one.
It's pink and cute.
I'm sure you'll love it.
Maybe I'll buy some boxer shorts for my dad.
What do you think?
I'll take these.
And I'll get these for me.
Do you think Dad will wear it?
Because I don't know. I don't know which one I'm gonna get him.
These are great.
Limited edition local pants.
Which one do you think is better... you or these?
I think I'd wear this one.
I'm sure you would.
Excuse me, please.
I'll pay you later.
Look, look, look.
He's so cute.
I knew Trixie was famous.
Here's your million yen refund.
Thank you very much.
I'll pay you later.
Pleasure.
I bought it.
We bought.
We bought hikikonyan goods.
I bought goods for my father.
I love Hiconyan, so I will give Hiconyan goods to Madoka Saito as a token of my appreciation.
That's very kind of you.
Aren't I being kind?
You're so kind. You're good, aren't you?
Here it is.
Yes, it's cute. I'll give this to Maboka. Will she be happy? It's cute. I was thinking of the heart-shaped one, but I thought she'd be more pleased with this one. Yes. I thought the heart one was cute, but I wondered which one would be better, and in the end I went with this one.
I hope your father will be happy too. He'll be happy, Dad. I'm sure he'll be moved. Nachu. Nachu. I hope you'll use it. I will.
Thank you for watching.